The Reese Family Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- The Oliver Family, 1839 - 1943; 7; Boxes: 59 - 69 Folders: 1 - 37, 1 - 9, 1 - 19, 1 - 16, 1 - 23, 1 - 18, 1 - 11, 1 - 16, 1 - 21, 1 - 27
  - Robert Shaw Oliver, 1887 - 1935; 7.2; About X linear feet Boxes: 59 - 63 Folders: 22 - 37, 1 - 9, 1 - 19, 1 - 16, 1 - 6
    - Miscellany, 1887 - 1935; 7.2.2; Boxes: 61 - 63 Folders: 16 - 19, 1 - 16, 1 - 6
      - Newspaper clippings (appointment of Robert Shaw Oliver as Assistant Secretary of War), 1903 (Folder 1, Box 63)
      - Newspaper clippings (obituaries for Robert Shaw Oliver), 1935 (Folder 2, Box 63)
      - Newspaper clippings (Cora Lyman Oliver’s wedding to Joseph Choate, 1903 (Folder 3, Box 63)
      - Newspaper clippings (Marion Lucy Oliver) [includes newspaper photograph of Marion Lucy Oliver], 1904 (Folder 4, Box 63)
      - Newspaper clippings [includes newspaper photograph of Robert Shaw Oliver], 1900 - 1905 (Folder 5, Box 63)
      - Newspaper clipping on the death of Brigadier General Robert Shaw Oliver with photo [copy only, original in Willis Reese Papers], circa 1935 (Folder 6, Box 63)
  - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, 1887 - 1943; 7.3; Boxes: 63 - 66 Folders: 7 - 23, 1 - 18, 1 - 11, 1 - 23
    Series contains correspondence and manuscript materials
    - Correspondence, 1887 - 1943; 7.3.1; Boxes: 63 - 64 Folders: 7 - 23, 1 - 18
      - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] to Hubertja “Bertie” Prayn [letters sent while Elizabeth lived in Europe and Bertie lived in Albany, New York], 1887 - 1888 (Folder 7, Box 63)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] to Hubertja “Bertie” Prayn [letters sent while Elizabeth lived in Europe and Bertie lived in Albany, New York], 1889 (Folder 8, Box 63)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] to Hubertja “Bertie” Prayn [letters sent while Elizabeth lived in Europe and Bertie lived in Albany, New York], 1890 (Folder 9, Box 63)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] to Hubertja “Bertie” Prayn [letters sent while Elizabeth lived in Europe and Bertie lived in Albany, New York], circa 1887 - 1890 (Folder 10, Box 63)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] to Hubertja “Bertie” Prayn [letter regarding Elizabeth’s impending marriage to Francis Kerby Stevens], circa 1907 (Folder 11, Box 63)
      - Hubertja “Bertie” Prayn to Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens], 1888 (Folder 12, Box 63)
      - Hubertja “Bertie” Prayn to Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, 1914 (Folder 13, Box 63)
      - Marion Rathbone Oliver to daughter, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] [letters sent while Elizabeth was studying at Miss Groton’s School in Boston], 1894 - 1895 (Folder 14, Box 63)
      - Marion Rathbone Oliver to daughter, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] [letters sent while Elizabeth was studying at Miss Groton’s School in Boston], circa 1894 (Folder 15, Box 63)
      - Marion Rathbone Oliver to daughter, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens], 1900 (Folder 16, Box 63)
      - Marion Rathbone Oliver to daughter, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [letters regarding Elizabeth’s marriage and birth of her first child, Elizabeth Shaw Stevens], circa 1907 - 1909 (Folder 17, Box 63)
      - Robert Shaw Oliver to daughter, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [letters regarding birth of Elizabeth’s first child, Elizabeth Shaw Stevens], 1909 (Folder 18, Box 63)
      - Robert Shaw Oliver to daughter, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [letters sent from Bermuda where Robert spent the winter], circa 1930s (Folder 19, Box 63)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] to brother John Rathbone Oliver, 1889 (Folder 20, Box 63)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] to brother John Rathbone Oliver, 1892 - 1893 (Folder 21, Box 63)
      - John Rathbone Oliver to sister, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] [letters sent while John was studying at Harvard and teaching at St. Paul’s School in New Hampshire, 1894, 1899 (Folder 22, Box 63)
      - John Rathbone Oliver to sister, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] [letters sent while John was studying at Harvard and teaching at St. Paul’s School in New Hampshire, circa 1890s (Folder 23, Box 63)
      - Cora Lyman Oliver to sister, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, undated (Folder 1, Box 64)
      - Marion Lucy Oliver to sister, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [Marion lived with her father Robert Shaw Oliver in Bermuda and Maryland], 1926 - 1932 (Folder 2, Box 64)
      - Francis Kerby Stevens to fiancée, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, 1907 (Folder 3, Box 64)
      - Francis Kerby Stevens to wife, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [letters sent to Murray Bay, Canada where Elizabeth is recovering from an illness; Francis remained in New Jersey with their baby], 1909 (Folder 4, Box 64)
      - Francis Kerby Stevens to wife, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, 1915 - 1916 (Folder 5, Box 64)
      - Francis Kerby Stevens to wife, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, 1919 (Folder 6, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens to mother, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, 1919, undated (Folder 7, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens to mother, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens and father, Francis Kerby Stevens, undated (Folder 8, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens to sister, Frances Gallatin Stevens, undated (Folder 9, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens to daughter, Frances Gallatin Stevens [Reese] [letters sent to Frances while she attended the Foxcroft School in Virginia], 1933 (Folder 10, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens to daughter, Frances Gallatin Stevens [Reese] [letters sent to Frances while she attended the Foxcroft School in Virginia], 1934 (Folder 11, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens to daughter, Frances Gallatin Stevens [Reese] [letters sent to Frances while she attended the Foxcroft School in Virginia], 1934 (Folder 12, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens to daughter, Frances Gallatin Stevens [Reese] [letters sent to Frances while she attended the Foxcroft School in Virginia], 1935 (Folder 13, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Stevens to daughter, Frances Gallatin Stevens Reese [letters sent to Frances while she attended the Foxcroft School in Virginia], circa 1937 - 1939 (Folder 14, Box 64)
      - Family correspondence, 1935, undated (Folder 15, Box 64)
      - Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens] to the Bowditch family, 1889 (Folder 16, Box 64)
      - Sir Mortimer Durand to Elizabeth Shaw Oliver [Stevens], 1907 (Folder 17, Box 64)
      - Private Lambert Vaile to Francis Kerby Stevens, 1941 (Folder 18, Box 64)
    - Manuscript materials, 7.3.2; Boxes: 65 - 66 Folders: 1 - 11, 1 - 23
      - “Her Sense of Humanity” by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 27 pages], undated (Folder 1, Box 65)
      - "Aunt Eliza’s Funeral" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 10 pages], undated (Folder 2, Box 65)
      - "Czadia" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 30 pages], undated (Folder 3, Box 65)
      - "The Magic Spectacles: A fairy story" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 4 pages], undated (Folder 4, Box 65)
      - "The Wonder Song" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 5 pages], undated (Folder 5, Box 65)
      - "The Buccaneers" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 55 pages], undated (Folder 6, Box 65)
      - Untitled story by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 22 pages], undated (Folder 7, Box 65)
      - Untitled story by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 23 pages], undated (Folder 8, Box 65)
      - Untitled story by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 21 pages], undated (Folder 9, Box 65)
      - "The Brotherhood of Pan" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 7 pages], undated (Folder 10, Box 65)
      - "Gardening" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten story], undated (Folder 11, Box 65)
      - "Amacameca: A Mexican sketch" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 7 pages], undated (Folder 12, Box 65)
      - "An introduction to the Salmon Salar" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten manuscript], undated (Folder 13, Box 65)
      - "A Modern Women’s Privilege" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, undated (Folder 14, Box 65)
      - "St. Catherine of Sienna" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten manuscript; 42 pages], undated (Folder 15, Box 65)
      - "Modern Sport" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten manuscript; 22 pages], undated (Folder 16, Box 65)
      - "A Moment’s Halt" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [3 typewritten and handwritten copies], undated (Folder 17, Box 65)
      - "Little Foxes" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten synopsis of chapters], undated (Folder 18, Box 65)
      - "Coq and Coquette" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten short story; 17 pages], undated (Folder 19, Box 65)
      - “A Smelly Drama in Seven Whiffs” (Murray Bay before the coming of the smell) by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten manuscript; 8 pages], undated (Folder 20, Box 65)
      - "Greenhorn’s Luck" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [typewritten short story; 10 pages], undated (Folder 21, Box 65)
      - "Salt of the Earth" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [typewritten manuscript; 14 pages], undated (Folder 22, Box 65)
      - "Saint Fidele" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [typewritten manuscript of a novel], undated (Folder 23, Box 65)
      - "Saint Fidele" by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten manuscript of a novel], undated (Folder 1, Box 66)
      - "The Feet of the Young Men," a poem by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [typewritten manuscript; 5 pages], undated (Folder 2, Box 66)
      - A Christmas poem by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, undated (Folder 3, Box 66)
      - Poem about beagle dogs by Mrs. Steven’s [handwritten manuscript], undated (Folder 4, Box 66)
      - Untitled poem by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, undated (Folder 5, Box 66)
      - “The Soup Tureen,” a play by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten in notebook], undated (Folder 6, Box 66)
      - Poems and songs by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten in notebook], undated (Folder 7, Box 66)
      - Poems and essays by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens [handwritten in notebook], undated (Folder 8, Box 66)
      - "Picking up the Pieces" [typewritten script of a play by an unidentified author], undated (Folder 9, Box 66)
      - “The Peytons of Virginia” [typewritten script of a play by an unidentified author], undated (Folder 10, Box 66)
      - Diary of Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, undated (Folder 11, Box 66)
    - Published articles, 7.3.3; Boxes: 67 Folders: 1 - 3
      - “Aunt Eliza’s Funeral” by Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens, undated (Folder 1, Box 67)
      - Four published chapters of the novel “Saint Fidele” originally printed as short stories, undated (Folder 2, Box 67)
      - Oliver, Elizabeth Shaw. “Tite Sauvage.” The Century Magazine (December 1907): 173-179. (Folder 3, Box 67)
    - Miscellany, 1896 - 1936; 7.3.4; Box: 67 Folder: 4
      - Guest book for vacation home in Pointe a Pic, Quebec, Canada near Murray Bay; includes pictures and signatures of guests, including relatives, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver, Robert Shaw Oliver, John Rathbone Oliver, Mary Rathbone, the Choates, the Bowditches, and others: Harold Jefferson Coolidge, the Sturgises, Elizabeth Ogden Adams, the Van Rensselaers, 1896 - 1936 (Folder 4, Box 67)
  - John Rathbone Oliver, 1887 - 1943; 7.4; Boxes: 67 - 69 Folders: 5 - 16, 1 - 21, 1 - 27
    Series contains personal and professional correspondence, writings, St. Pauls School materials, Harvard University Materials, Miscellany, photographs, and a scrapbook
    - Personal correspondence, 1885 - 1940; 7.4.1; Box: 67 Folders: 5 - 16
      - Letters from John Rathbone Oliver to his family, 1885 - 1886 (Folder 5, Box 67)
      - Letters from Elizabeth Shaw Oliver to her brother, John Rathbone Oliver, 1889 - 1891 (Folder 6, Box 67)
      - Letters from Marion Rathbone Oliver to her son John Rathbone Oliver [while John was at St. Paul’s School in New Hampshire and Harvard University], 1889 - 1894 (Folder 7, Box 67)
      - Letters from Marion Rathbone Oliver to her son, John Rathbone Oliver [while John was at St. Paul’s School in New Hampshire and Harvard], 1889 - 1894 (Folder 8, Box 67)
      - Letters from John Rathbone Oliver to his father, Robert Shaw Oliver [while John was in France], 1890 (Folder 9, Box 67)
      - Letters from Marion Lucy Oliver to her brother, John Rathbone Oliver, 1889 - 1895 (Folder 10, Box 67)
      - Letters from Cora Lyman Oliver to her brother, John Rathbone Oliver, 1889 - 1892 (Folder 11, Box 67)
      - Letter to Hubertja “Bertie” Prayn from John Rathbone Oliver, circa 1908 (Folder 12, Box 67)
      - Letter from friends to John Rathbone Oliver, 1936 (Folder 13, Box 67)
      - Letters to Elizabeth Shaw Oliver Stevens from her brother, John Rathbone Oliver [sent from the Hartford retreat where John was a patient], 1940 (Folder 14, Box 67)
      - Letters from Marion Rathbone Oliver to her son, John Rathbone Oliver, undated (Folder 15, Box 67)
      - Letters from grandmother and uncle to John Rathbone Oliver, undated (Folder 16, Box 67)
    - Professional correspondence, 7.4.2; Boxes: 68 Folders: 1 - 3
      - 1 letter each from St. Paul’s School and Harvard University to John Rathbone Oliver, 1894 (Folder 1, Box 68)
      - Letter from the Bishop of Albany, W. C. Doane, stating he will nominate John Rathbone for entry to a holy order to become a priest, 1895 (Folder 2, Box 68)
      - Letters to John Rathbone Oliver regarding the publication and production of his work, 1894 - 1919 (Folder 3, Box 68)
    - Writings by John Rathbone Oliver, 7.4.3; Box: 68 Folders: 4 - 18
      - Seven chapters of an untitled novel (folder 1 of 2) [handwritten draft], undated (Folder 4, Box 68)
      - Seven chapters of an untitled novel (folder 1 of 2) [handwritten draft], undated (Folder 5, Box 68)
      - “Rose of the Forest” [handwritten draft], undated (Folder 6, Box 68)
      - “Criminal law and procedure in Europe, report of a Committee of the American Institute of Criminal Law” [publication], 1920 (Folder 7, Box 68)
      - “Criminology and common Sense” [publication and handwritten draft], circa 1924 (Folder 8, Box 68)
      - “A democracy of Aristocrats” [typewritten draft], undated (Folder 9, Box 68)
      - “Hippocrates,” a paper evaluating a collection of Hippocrates’s writing donated to John Hopkins University [typewritten draft], undated (Folder 10, Box 68)
      - “The psychiatry of Hippocrates: A plea for the study of the history of medicine” [typewritten manuscript], 1925 April 9 (Folder 11, Box 68)
      - Lecture at the University of Maryland, 1927 April 28 (Folder 12, Box 68)
      - “The Promethean Fantasies of Scriabine,” a reprint from the Bulletin of the Institute of History of Medicine, 1933 (Folder 13, Box 68)
      - “Personal Reminiscences of Stephen D’Irsay,” article published in the Bulletin of the Institute of History of Medicine, undated (Folder 14, Box 68)
      - “Spontaneous Combustion - a Literary Curiosity” [typewritten manuscript], 1948 May (Folder 15, Box 68)
      - “Spirit of the Jesuit” [carbon copy of a typewritten manuscript], undated (Folder 16, Box 68)
      - Three poems, undated (Folder 17, Box 68)
      - Preface to a book discussing medical history [typewritten manuscript], undated (Folder 18, Box 68)
    - St. Paul’s School, 7.4.4; Box: 68 Folders: 19 - 20
      - Library fine notice, 1889 (Folder 19, Box 68)
      - Toast to the school curriculum, undated (Folder 20, Box 68)
    - Harvard University, 1888 - 1899; 7.4.5; Boxes: 68 - 69 Folders: 21, 1 - 15
      - “Granada,” a play by John Rathbone Oliver [photographs], 1894 (Folder 21, Box 68)
      - “Granada,” a play by John Rathbone Oliver [programs, 1 telegram], 1894 (Folder 1, Box 69)
      - “Granada,” a play by John Rathbone Oliver [reviews], 1894 (Folder 2, Box 69)
      - “Fabulae Latinae” [program for play], 1894 (Folder 3, Box 69)
      - “Fabulae Latinae” [reviews], 1894 (Folder 4, Box 69)
      - “The Harvard Advocate” [3 issues], 1892 June 25, 1892 June 29, 1894 June 28 (Folder 5, Box 69)
      - “The Class Poem” by John Rathbone Oliver [newspaper clipping], 1894 (Folder 6, Box 69)
      - Note from Mary Rathbone to her grandson John Rathbone Oliver, undated (Folder 7, Box 69)
      - Letter to John Rathbone Oliver regarding the play, “Fabulae Latinae”, circa 1894 (Folder 8, Box 69)
      - Poems by John Rathbone Oliver, undated (Folder 9, Box 69)
      - Phi Beta Kappa Junior class dinner (Class of 1894) [poem by John Rathbone Oliver and program for the event], 1893 (Folder 10, Box 69)
      - Invitations, undated (Folder 11, Box 69)
      - Article published in “The Churchman”, 1895 February 16 (Folder 12, Box 69)
      - Miscellaneous writings, undated (Folder 13, Box 69)
      - “Horae Scholasticae”, 1888 December 19 (Folder 14, Box 69)
      - Interior of the Cathedral of All Saints, Albany, New York [photograph], circa 1890s (Folder 15, Box 69)
    - Miscellany, 1887 - 1943; 7.4.6; Box: 69 Folders: 16 - 27
      - Newspaper clippings collected during his tenure as chief medical officer to the courts of the city of Baltimore, 1924 - 1925 (Folder 16, Box 69)
      - Obituary notices regarding the death of John Rathbone Oliver [includes church bulletin notices], 1943 (Folder 17, Box 69)
      - American International Academy, International [honorary diploma], 1930 May 8 (Folder 18, Box 69)
      - Prayers [includes Italian language], undated (Folder 19, Box 69)
      - Christmas cards, undated (Folder 20, Box 69)
      - Watercolors, circa 1887 (Folder 21, Box 69)
      - Pi Gamma Mu (National Social Science Honor Society) certificate, 1928 December 10 (Folder 22, Box 69)
      - Postcard album [“Postkarten Album”]; “Tuscan Cards. Vol. I. Perugia (illustrating my notes on Mataratzzo’s Chronicles of the Baglioni Family), Assisi (also illustrating my notes), Spello, Foligno, Monte Falco, and Spoletto, and part of Orvietto. August, September, 1903.” [includes Italian language] (Folder 23, Box 69)
      - Three postcards depicting a 1912 lynching the Albany State Capitol Building and a Kentucky prison hospital, 1909 - 1912 (Folder 24, Box 69)
      - Postcards of hospital scenes most likely in Austria during John Rathbone Oliver’s medical studies, circa 1910 (Folder 25, Box 69)
      - Three postcards from friends to John Rathbone Oliver, undated (Folder 26, Box 69)
      - Scrapbook compiled by John Rathbone Oliver [includes programs, newspaper clippings, correspondence and photographs], 1925 - 1932 (Folder 27, Box 69)
    - Photographs, 7.4.7
    - Scrapbook, 7.4.8
- Graphic Materials, 1850 - 1984; 8; Boxes: 70 - 76 Folders: 1 - 54, 1 - 65, 1 - 81, 1- 46, 1 - 35, 1 - 11, 1 - 17
  Series contains family portraits and graphic materials pretaining to the Reese family, the Stevens Family, the Davie family, the Rathbone family, and the Oliver family.
  - Family Portraits, 1930 - 1938; 8.1; Boxes: 70 Folders: 1 - 2
    - Oliver/Stevens Family Portrait, Murray Bay, Quebec, Canada; Birthday of Robert Shaw Stevens; Standing - left to right: Francis Kerby Stevens (married to Elizabeth Shaw Oliver), Joseph H. Choate (married to Cora Oliver), John Rathbone Oliver, Joseph Choate, Jr., (‘Sandy’ with pipe - son of Cora), Charles Harding (husband of Marion Choate) Seated - middle row: Marion Lucy Oliver, Elizabeth Shaw Oliver (wife of Francis Kerby Stevens), Robert Shaw Oliver, Cora Oliver (wife of Joseph H. Choate), Marion Choate (wife of Charles Harding - daughter of Cora) Front Row: Frances Gallatin Stevens [Reese] (daughter of Elizabeth and Francis), Elizabeth Stevens (daughter of Elizabeth and Francis), Helen Choate (later married Geoffrey Platt), Priscilla Choate (later married Penrose Hallowell), circa 1930 (Folder 1, Box 70)
    - Reese/Willis Family Portrait, Christmas 1938; Standing - left to right: Frances S. Reese (wife of Willis Reese), Anita S. Willis (wife of Harold), Harold Willis (standing behind), Agnes Willis (wife of Reginald, deceased), William Willis Reese (father of Willis Reese - standing behind in cap), Alice Reese Richards (Mrs. Guy Richards), Willis L.M. Reese, Arthur Willis Margaret Mesier Reese Seated back center: Anita Willis (daughter of Anita and Harold, now Mrs. Lester Vivian), Charles Willis (son of Arthur) Seated front: Dicky Willis (holding “tag” - son of Reginald), Adele Willis (daughter of Harold), Vallery Willis (daughter of Reginald), Ruth Willis (wife of Arthur), Augusta Bliss Reese (holding ‘satsuma’ - wife of William Willis Reese), Arthur Willis (son of Arthur), missing: Bobby Willis (son of Harold) (Folder 2, Box 70)
  - The Reese Family, 1953 - 1984; 8.2; About X linear feet Boxes: 70 - 71 Folders: 3 - 54, 1 - 65
    Series contains materials pretainng to Willis L.M. Reese, Frances Stevens Reese, ancestors of Willis L.M. Reese, possible ancestors, children, on board the Trimaran with the Fred Osborns and more, and miscellany.
    - Willis L.M. Reese, 1953 - 1984; 8.2.1; Box: 70 Folders: 3 - 14
      - Willis Reese, Frances Reese and family at Obercreek, 2 photos; Verso: souvenir of a happy day! Clarkson, WLMR, FSR, Obercreek, July 11th, 1953, Love from Olive, 1953 July 11 (Folder 3, Box 70)
      - Portrait of Willis Livingston Mesier Reese, undated (Folder 4, Box 70)
      - Portrait of Willis Livingston Mesier Reese, undated (Folder 5, Box 70)
      - Portrait of Willis Livingston Mesier Reese, undated (Folder 6, Box 70)
      - Portrait of Willis Livingston Mesier Reese, undated (Folder 7, Box 70)
      - Two portraits of Willis Livingston Mesier Reese [oversized], undated (Folder 8, Box 70)
      - Newspaper clipping with photo of Willis Reese concerning the Red Feather Ball for the Five Towns United Fund campaign, 1961 - 1962 (Folder 9, Box 70)
      - Photo of Willis Reese during an event concerning the United Nations, most likely the World Court, undated (Folder 10, Box 70)
      - Photo of Willis Reese during an event concerning the United Nations, most likely the World Court, undated (Folder 11, Box 70)
      - Christmas Photo folder, contained files 15 and 16; Verso: Willis selling Grinnell Books, 1984 (Folder 12, Box 70)
      - Willis selling Grinnell Books; Verso: To Mr. Reese, “Eyes” have it! Merry Christmas, Love, The Kolthay-Feldmans; The Joseph McDonald 10k Memorial Race, Wappinger Falls, New York July 8th, 1984 - 26/26A, 1984 July 8 (Folder 13, Box 70)
      - Willis selling Grinnell Books; Verso: To Mr. Reese, Merry Christmas, Love, The Kolthay-Feldmans; The Joseph McDonald 10k Memorial Race, Wappinger Falls, New York July 8th, 1984 - 27/27A, 1984 July 8 (Folder 14, Box 70)
    - Frances Stevens Reese, 8.2.2; Box: 70 Folders: 15 - 29
      - Photo of Frances Reese with other woman, undated (Folder 15, Box 70)
      - Photo of Frances Reese behind microphone with other woman, undated (Folder 16, Box 70)
      - Small portraits of Frances Reese from included envelope label Mrs. Reese, undated (Folder 17, Box 70)
      - Large black and white portrait of Frances Reese, undated (Folder 18, Box 70)
      - Small portrait of Frances Reese, undated (Folder 19, Box 70)
      - Frances Reese with Marist President Dennis Murray among others at Val-Kill, the Eleanor Roosevelt National Historic Site (with paper frame), 1996 October (Folder 20, Box 70)
      - Frances Reese with Joan Rivers, Marist President Dennis Murray among others at Val-Kill, the Eleanor Roosevelt National Historic Site (with paper frame), 1996 October (Folder 21, Box 70)
      - Frances Reese with Marist President Dennis Murray among others at Val-Kill, the Eleanor Roosevelt National Historic Site (with paper frame), 1996 October (Folder 22, Box 70)
      - Envelope that contained files 25 and 26, labeled Val-Kill 10/96, 1996 October (Folder 23, Box 70)